RG 089, Department of Transportation
Connecticut State Library
Department of Transportation records
1941-2003, bulk 1973-2003
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Dept. of Transportation
266.75 cubic feet
The Department of Transportation was created in 1969 per P.A. 768, sec. 3, with the merger for four agencies: State Highway Department, Department of Aeronautics, Connecticut Transportation Authority, and the Commissioners of Steamship Terminals.
RG089
Multiple
Historical Note
The Department of Transportation was created in 1969 per P.A. 768, sec. 3, with the merger for four agencies: State Highway Department, Department of Aeronautics, Connecticut Transportation Authority, and the Commissioners of Steamship Terminals.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Included here are Tolls and concessions, log books 1942-1988; records of the Commissioner, 1941-2003, bulk 1973-2003; photographs, 1988-1989; Bureau of Aeronautics, Bradley International Airport, Automatically Controlled Transportation, 1974-1975; Mianus River Bridge Collapse investigation, 1983; Legislative proposals, 1994; and Films, 1973-1996. The bulk of the films are road logs.
Arrangement
Series numbers used here are those previously assigned within RG 089 in its entirety and therefore the series described here are not numbered consecutively.
Series 22. Tolls and Concessions, 1942-1988, 51 cubic feet
Series 25. Commissioner, 1941-2003, bulk 1973-2003.
Accession 1994-022, 1986-1990, 27 cubic feet
Accession 2002-093, 1991-1994, 22 cubic feet
Accession 2004-021, 1994-1998, 17 cubic feet
Accession 2007-038, 1998-2004, 18 cubic feet
Accession 2007-041, 1941-2003, bulk 1978-2003, 4 cubic feet
Series 33. Photographs, 1988-1989, .5 cubic feet
Series 34. Bureau of Aeronautics. Bradley International Airport. Automatically Controlled Transportation (ACT), 1974-1975, Accession: 1997-013, 2.75 cubic feet
Series 35. Mianus River Bridge Collapse Investigation, 1983, Accession: 2001-006, .5 cubic feet
Series 36. Legislative Proposals, 1994, Accession: 1999-094, 1 folder
Series 38. Films, 1973-1996, 124 cubic feet
Related Material
RG 089:001, State Highway Department, 1894-1975
RG 089:010, State Boundary Line Perambulations, 1965-1997
RG 089:011, Aerial photographs, see the Research Guide to Aerial Photographs at the Connecticut State Library
RG 089:024, Connecticut Transportation Authority, 1956-1973
RG 089:030, State Traffic Commission, 1935-1995
RG 089:031, Connecticut Public Transportation Commission, 1980-2001
RG 089:032, Transportation Accountability Board, 1986-1987
RG 089:037, Commissioners of Steamship Terminals, 1915
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Dept. of Transportation; Connecticut. State Highway Dept
Subjects:
Transportation -- Connecticut; Bradley International Airport (Windsor Locks, Conn.); Airports -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks; Intra-airport transportation; Bridge failures -- Connecticut -- Greenwich; Mianus River Bridge (Greenwich, Conn.); Bridges -- Connecticut -- Greenwich; Bridges -- Mianus River; Interstate 95 -- Connecticut -- Greenwich; Housatonic Railroad; Tolls -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Correspondence; Film (material by form); Reports; Photographs
Restrictions on Access
Some of these records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 22. Tolls and Concessions, 1942-1988; 51 cubic feet
  - Log books, 1942-1988; 1989-011
    - Branford, 1980-1981; 2 items (Box 198)
    - Charter Oak Bridge
      Logs for 1945-1958 are labeled as C.O.B., 1958-1962 are labeled as Greater Hartford Bridge Authority, and 1962-1978 are labeled as Hartford Area Toll Bridges.
      - 1942 September 5-1943 January 29 (Box Item 1)
      - 1943 January 31-June 28 (Box Item 2)
      - 1943 June 30-1944 January 1 (Box Item 3)
      - 1944 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 4)
      - 1945 January 1-1946 January 1 (Box Item 5)
      - 1946 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 6)
      - 1947 January 1-December 30 (Box Item 7)
      - 1947 December 30-1948 (Box Item 8)
      - 1948 December 30-1949 (Box Item 9)
      - 1950-1951 January 1 (Box Item 10)
      - 1951 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 11)
      - 1952 (Box Item 12)
      - 1953-1954 January 1 (Box Item 13)
      - 1954 (Box Item 14)
      - 1955-1956 January 1 (Box Item 15)
      - 1956 January 2-1957 January 1 (Box Item 16)
      - 1957 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 17)
      - 1958 (Box Item 18)
      - 1958 October 27-1959 September 29 (Box Item 19)
      - 1959 July 2-September 24 (Box Item 20)
      - 1959 (Box Item 21)
      - 1960 (Box Item 22)
      - 1961 January 1-1962 January 1 (Box Item 23)
      - 1962 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 24)
      - 1963 January 1-December 30 (Box Item 25)
      - 1963 December 31-1964 December 30 (Box Item 26)
      - 1965 January 2-December 31 (Box Item 27)
      - 1966 (Box Item 28)
      - 1967 (Box Item 29)
      - 1968 (Box Item 30)
      - 1969 (Box Item 31)
      - 1970 (Box Item 32)
      - 1971 January 1-December 30 (Box Item 33)
      - 1972-1975, 4 items (Box 907)
      - 1976-1981, 6 items (Box 906)
      - 1982-1988, 7 items (Box 905)
    - Greenwich Parkway
      - 1943 January 1-1944 May 15 (Box Item 34)
      - 1947-1952 May 2, 12 items (Box 202)
      - 1949-1953, 14 items (Box 195)
      - 1954-1956 March 31, 1960, 13 items (Box 196)
      - 1961-1963 March 31, 9 items (Box 197)
      - 1963 April 1-1964, 7 items (Box 198)
      - 1965-1967 August 31, 10 items (Box 203)
      - 1967 September 1-1970 July 31, 6 items (Box 204)
      - 1970 August 1-1973 July 31, 7 items (Box 205)
      - 1973 August 1-1976, 7 items (Box 206)
      - 1977-1979, 6 items (Box 207)
      - 1980-1983 June 30, 7 items (Box 208)
      - 1983 July 1-1988 June 28, 10 items (Box 209)
    - Greenwich Turnpike
      - 1958-1963, 1972, 1975-1979, 8 items (Box 101)
      - 1980-1985, 7 items (Box 102)
    - Madison, 1959 January 1-1959 May 15, 1985; 2 items (Box 201)
    - Milford Parkway
      - 1972-1974 September, 11 items (Box 901)
      - 1974 October-1977 July, 11 items (Box 902)
      - 1977 July-1981, 7 items (Box 903)
      - 1982-1988, 8 items (Box 904)
      - Construction log, 1987-1988; 1 item (Box 904)
    - Montville, 1977, 1985; 2 items (Box 201)
    - Norwalk, 1959, 1985; 2 items (Box 201)
    - Plainfield Turnpike
      - 1958-1963, 6 items (Box 801)
      - 1964-1969, 6 items (Box 802)
      - 1970-1975, 6 items (Box 803)
      - 1976-1981, 6 items (Box 804)
      - 1982-1985, 4 items (Box 805)
    - Putnam Bridge
      - 1965-1970, 6 items (Box 911)
      - 1971-1975, 6 items (Box 912)
      - 1976-1978, 3 items (Box 913)
      - 1979-1985, 7 items (Box 908)
    - Stratford Turnpike
      - 1960-1964, 6 items (Box 301)
      - 1965-1969, 5 items (Box 302)
      - 1970-1975, 6 items (Box 303)
      - 1976-1980, 5 items (Box 304)
      - 1981-1982, 1984-1985 November 1, 4 items (Box 305)
    - Wallingford Parkway
      - 1979-1984, 37 items (Box 910)
      - 1980-1982, 1984-1987, 65 items (Box 909)
      - 1988, 1 item (Box 904)
    - West Haven, 1961, 1985; 2 items (Box 201)
  - Log books, 1958-1959, 1985; 1989-014
    - Bissell Bridge, 1985; 1 item (Box 501)
    - Branford, 1958, 1985; 2 items (Box 501)
    - Unidentified, 1958-1959; 2 items (Box 501)
- Series 25. Commissioner, 1941-2003, bulk 1973-2003; 88 cubic feet
  - 1994-022
    Commissioners J.W. Burns and Emil H. Frankel.
    - Correspondence to State Legislators, 1986-1990
      - Corresondence to State Representatives
        - Districts number 1-26, 29-35, 37-79 (Box 1)
        - Districts number 80-88, 90-99, 101-109, 111-117, 119-122, 126, 131, 133-149, 151 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence to State Senators, Districts number 1-36, 1987-1990 (Box 3)
    - Corresopndence to town officials and constituents
      - Andover - Guilford, 1986-1990 (Box 4)
      - Haddam - Norwalk, 1987-1990 (Box 5)
      - Norwich - Weston, 1984-1990 (Box 6)
      - Westport - Woodstock, 1986-1990 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence to other states, 1983-1990 (Box 7)
      Arranged by first letter.
    - Dept. of Transportation Bureau correspondence, 1985-1990
      - Bureau of Administration, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Aviation, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Ports, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Engineering & Highway Operations, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Policy & Planning, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Public Transportation, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
      - Affirmative Action, 19865-1990 (Box 8)
      - Commuinications, 1985-1990 (Box 8)
      - Management Services, 1985-1990 (Box 8)
      - Transportation 2020 Forum (Box 8)
      - Commissioner Burns memos, 1985-1991 (Box 15)
      - John Drake memos, 1987-1989 (Box 15)
      - Deputy Commissioner Lazarek Memos, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
      - Planning & Research, 1977-1982 (Box 15)
      - State Traffic Commission, 1981 (Box 15)
      - Internal Administration Control Office, 1981 (Box 15)
      - Highways, 1988-1990 (Box 15)
      - Highways, 1986-1990; 4 folders (Box 16)
      - High Speed Rail, 1986-1991 (Box 16)
      - New Haven Line, 1975-1990 (Box 17)
      - Housatonic Railroad Company, 1987 (Box 17)
      - Guilford Transportation Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 17)
      - Conrail, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
      - Metro North, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
      - Bradley International Airport Commission (Box 17)
      - Bradley International Airport (Box 17)
      - Airport general (Box 17)
      - Bureau of Aeronautics, 3 folders (Box 17)
      - Airport licenses (Box 17)
      - Aircraft purchase (Box 17)
      - Airports: Brainard, Danielson, Jonnycake, Robertson, Sikorsky, Oxford, Windham (Box 17)
      - Bureau of Aeronautics general, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Arthur Andersen & Co., 1982-1984 (Box 18)
      - Ramp congestion photos (Box 18)
    - Interdepartment correspondence, 1983-1990
      - Adjutant General (Box 9)
      - Administrative Services, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Aging (Box 9)
      - Agriculture (Box 9)
      - Attorney General's Office, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 9)
      - Board of Education & Services for the Blind (Box 9)
      - Bond Commission (Box 9)
      - Chief State's Attorney (Box 9)
      - Comptroller (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Public Transportation Commission (Box 10)
      - Consumer Protection (Box 10)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 10)
      - Economic Development (Box 10)
      - Education (Box 10)
      - Environmental Protection (Box 10)
      - Ethics Commission (Box 10)
      - Finance Advisory Committee (Box 10)
      - Fiscal Analysis (Box 10)
      - General Assembly, 4 folders (Box 10)
      - Legislative Program Review & Investigation Committee (Box 10)
      - Public Special Acts (Box 10)
      - Regulations Review Committee (Box 10)
      - Transportation Committee, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Governor's Office Annual (Box 10)
      - Governor's Counsel on Voluntary Action (Box 10)
      - Governor's Dept. of Transportation press releases (Box 10)
      - Governor's Office general (Box 12)
      - Governor's Office (Box 12)
      - Governor's Southeastern Office (Box 12)
      - Lt. Governor's Office (Box 12)
      - Governor's Washington Office (Box 12)
      - Health Department (Box 12)
      - Higher Education (Box 12)
      - Housing (Box 12)
      - Human Rights & Opprtunities Commission (Box 12)
      - Income Maintenance (Box 12)
      - Inspector General (Box 12)
      - Labor (Box 12)
      - Library (Box 12)
      - Mental Health (Box 12)
      - Mental Retardation (Box 12)
      - Military (Box 12)
      - Motor Vehicles (Box 12)
      - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women (Box 12)
      - Office of Policy & Management (Box 12)
      - Office of Policy & Management (Box 13)
      - Protection & Advocacy (Box 13)
      - Public Utilities Control (Box 13)
      - Public Safety (Box 13)
      - Public Works (Box 13)
      - Revenue Services (Box 13)
      - Safety Commission (Box 13)
      - Secretary of the State (Box 13)
      - Special Revenue Commission (Box 13)
      - State Properties Review Board, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - State Planning Council (Box 13)
      - State Treasurer (Box 13)
      - State Tax Dept. (Box 13)
      - State Attorney (Box 13)
      - Statewide Emergency Telecommunications (Box 13)
      - Standardization Committee (Box 13)
      - Standing Committee (Box 13)
      - Superior Court (Box 13)
      - Supreme Court (Box 13)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 13)
      - Veteran's Affairs (Box 13)
    - Governor's correspondence log sheets, 1986-1990; 7 bundles (Box 11)
    - Commissioner's correspondence log sheets, 1985-1990; 1 folder, 5 bundles (Box 14)
    - Subject Files, 1973-1991
      - Bridges miscellaneous (Box 19)
      - Charter Oak Bridge (Box 19)
      - Mianus River Bridge collapse (Box 19)
      - Orphan bridges (Box 19)
      - Central Connecticut Expressway (Box 19)
      - Code of Ethics (Box 19)
      - Code of Fair Practices (Box 19)
      - Committees (Box 19)
      - Massachusetts Transit Policy Committee (Box 19)
      - Commission on Future Operations of New Haven Line (Box 19)
      - Highway Modal Policy Committee (Box 19)
      - Public Transportation Policy Committee (Box 19)
      - Complaints (Box 19)
      - Concessions (Box 19)
      - Connecticut Transit (Box 19)
      - Consultant miscellaneous (Box 20)
      - Consultant engineer approvals (Box 20)
      - Consultant engineer disapprovals (Box 20)
      - Consultant selection process (Box 20)
      - Contract procedures (Box 20)
      - Contractors (Box 20)
      - Correspondence procedures (Box 20)
      - Disadvantaged Business Enterprise/Women Business Enterprise (DBE/WBE) (Box 20)
      - Delegation of Authority (Box 20)
      - Dept. of Transportation/Dept. of Administrative Services Capitol projects (Box 20)
      - Emergency declarations (Box 21)
      - Energy crisis (Box 21)
      - Equipment (Box 21)
      - Elderly & handicapped transportation (Box 21)
      - Environment (Box 21)
      - Equal employment opportunities (Box 21)
      - Facility Acceleration through Special Techniques (FAST) (Box 21)
      - Federal Highway and Public Transportation Improvement Act of 1978 (Box 21)
      - Flood 6.6.82 (Box 21)
      - Freight market development (Box 21)
      - Gasoline stations (Box 21)
      - Goal & objectives (Box 21)
      - Infrastructure renewal (Box 21)
      - Inter state trade-ins (Box 21)
      - Leases (Box 21)
      - Management incentive plan (Box 21)
      - Merritt Parkway (Box 21)
      - Minority Business Enterprises (Box 21)
      - Negotiations Committee (Box 21)
      - Northeast Corridor improvement project (Box 21)
      - Odd balls (Box 21)
      - Paving program hearing (Box 22)
      - Policy (Box 22)
      - Reorganization of Dept. of Transportation (Box 22)
      - Ridesharing (Box 22)
      - Savings bond campaign (Box 22)
      - Security Dept. of Transportation facilities (Box 22)
      - Signs (Box 22)
      - Special tax bond obligation (Box 22)
      - Speed limit (Box 22)
      - State vehicles (Box 22)
      - Statewide transportation planning process (Box 22)
      - Strategic planning (Box 22)
      - Tandem trailers (Box 22)
      - Telephone calling cards (Box 22)
      - Telephone (Box 22)
      - Tolls (Box 22)
      - Town aid (Box 22)
      - Travel authorizations (Box 22)
      - Union general (Box 22)
      - Union negotiations (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Employees Union Independent (Box 22)
      - Connecticut State Employees Association (Box 22)
      - Utilities (Box 22)
      - Vanpooling (Box 22)
    - Mianus River Bridge, 1983-1992
      - FHWA Claim, 1983-1990 (Box 23)
      - State Police investigation report (Box 23)
      - Connecticut Turnpike removal agreement (toll agreement), 1988 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence agreement, 1990-1992 (Box 23)
    - United States Government Correspondence, 1986-1990
      - Federal transit (Box 24)
      - Federal highway, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - U.S. Dept. of Environmental Protection (Box 25)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (Box 25)
      - U.S. Government general (Box 25)
      - U.S. Interior Dept. (Box 25)
      - U.S. Dept. of Transportation (Box 25)
      - Federal Railroad Administration (Box 25)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 25)
      - U.S. Congress, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Corresopndence to Associations and Committees, 1974-1990
      - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (AASHTO) (Box 26)
      - Capitol Region Council of Government (Box 26)
      - Connecticut Association of Streets & Highway (Box 26)
      - Construction Institute (Box 26)
      - Connecticut Engineers in Private Practice, Inc. (Box 26)
      - Connecticut Construction Industries Association, Inc. (Box 26)
      - Coalition of Northeastern Governors (Box 26)
      - Housatonic Valley Council of Elected Officials (Box 26)
      - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 26)
      - Greater Bridgeport Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - South Central Connecticut Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - Southern Connecticut Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - Southwestern Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - Windham Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - Tri-State Regional Planning Agency (Box 26)
      - Transportation Research Board (Box 26)
      - Transit districts general (Box 26)
      - Motor Transport Association (Box 26)
      - Metropolitan Transport Association (Box 26)
      - Northeastern Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (NASHTO) (Box 26)
      - National Governors' Association (Box 26)
      - National Governors' Association Hazardous Material Transportation (Box 26)
      - National Transportation Safety Board (Box 26)
      - Nationwide Public Project Coalition (Box 26)
      - New England Governors' Conference, Inc. (Box 26)
    - Commissioner's Drafts for the Governor's Signature, 1988-1990; 7 bundles (Box 27)
  - 2002-093
    - Correspondence to State Legislators, 1991-1994
      - Various Legislators (sent to more than two) (Box 1)
      - Correspondence to State Senators, Districts number 1-35 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence to State Representatives (Box 1)
        - Districts number 1-35 (Box 1)
        - Districts n umber 36-145 (Box 2)
        - Districts number 146-151 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence to town officials and constituents, 1991-1994 (Box 3)
      - Andover - East Hartford (Box 3)
      - East Haven - Meriden (Box 4)
      - Middlebury - Simsbury (Box 5)
      - Somers - Woodstock (Box 6)
    - Correspondence to other states, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
    - Interdepartment correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Adjutant General (Box 8)
      - Aging (Box 8)
      - Agriculture (Box 8)
      - Attorney General (Box 8)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 8)
      - Bond Commission (Box 8)
      - Central Connecticut State University (Box 8)
      - Chief State's Attorney (Box 8)
      - Chief Medical Examiner (Box 8)
      - Children & Youth Services (Box 8)
      - Commission on the Arts (Box 8)
      - Commission to Effect Government Reorganization (Box 8)
      - Comptroller (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Economic Conference Board (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Employment and Training Commission (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Public Transportation Commission (Box 8)
      - Consumer Protection (Box 8)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 8)
      - Developmental Disabilities Council (Box 8)
      - Economic Development (Box 8)
      - Education (Box 8)
      - Environmental Protection (Box 8)
      - Ethics Commission (Box 8)
      - Finance Advisory Commission (Box 8)
      - Fiscal Analysis (Box 8)
      - Freedom of Information Commission (Box 8)
      - General Assembly (Box 8)
      - General Assembly committees (Box 8)
        - Appropriations Committee (Box 8)
        - Finance Revenue & Bonding Committee (Box 9)
        - Regulations Review Committee (Box 9)
        - Transportation Committee (Box 9)
      - Governor (Box 9)
        - Governor's draft logs (Box 9)
        - The new Connecticut marketing campaign (Box 9)
        - Annual administrative reports (Box 9)
        - Governor's executive orders (Box 9)
        - Governor's Washington Office (Box 9)
        - Governor's weekly activity report (Box 9)
        - Lt. Governor's Office (Box 9)
      - Hazardous waste management service (Box 10)
      - Health, Department of (Box 10)
      - Higher Education (Box 10)
      - Historical Commission, Connecticut (Box 10)
      - Housing, Department of (Box 10)
      - Human Resources, Department of (Box 10)
      - Human Rights & Opportunities Commission (Box 10)
      - Human services cabinet (Box 10)
      - Income Maintenance, Department of (Box 10)
      - Information Technology, Department of (Box 10)
      - Inspector General (Box 10)
      - Insurance Department (Box 10)
      - Insurance Purchasing Board (Box 10)
      - Judicial Department (Box 10)
      - Labor, Department of (Box 10)
      - Library (Box 10)
      - Liquor Control (Box 10)
      - Mental Health, Department of (Box 10)
      - Mental Retardation, Department of (Box 10)
      - Military, Department of (Box 10)
      - Motor Vehicles, Department of (Box 10)
      - Permanent Commission on Status of Women (Box 10)
      - Policy and Management, Office of (Box 10)
      - Executive Bond Task Force (Box 10)
      - Progress Council (Box 10)
      - Protection & Advocacy for Handicapped & Developmentally Disabled Persons, Office of (Box 11)
      - Public Health and Addiction Services (Box 11)
      - Public Safety, Department of (Box 11)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 11)
      - Public Works, Department of (Box 11)
      - Revenue Services (Box 11)
      - Safety Commission (Box 11)
      - Secretary of the State (Box 11)
      - Social Services, Department of (Box 11)
      - Standardization Committee (Box 11)
      - Special Revenue, Department of (Box 11)
      - State Properties Review Board (Box 11)
      - State Siting Council (Box 11)
      - State Treasurer, Office of (Box 11)
      - State Tax Department (Box 11)
      - State's Attorney (Box 11)
      - Statewide Emergency Telecom (Box 11)
      - Superior Court (Box 11)
      - Superior Court Chief Justice (Box 11)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 11)
      - Veteran's Affairs, Department of (Box 11)
      - Workman's Compensation (Box 11)
    - Department of Transportation Bureau Correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Finance & Administration, Bureau of (Box 12)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 12)
      - Aviation (Box 12)
      - Ports (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Coastline Port Authority (Box 12)
      - State Pier (Box 12)
      - Commissioner's memoranda (Box 12)
      - Deputy Commissioner's memoranda (Box 12)
      - Communication, Director of (Box 12)
      - State Traffic Commission (Box 12)
      - Plainville Mall (Box 12)
      - Management Services (Box 12)
      - Engineering & Highway Operations, Bureau of (Box 12)
      - Maintenance (Box 12)
      - Policy & Planning, Bureau of (Box 12)
      - Public Transportation, Bureau of (Box 12)
      - Bradley International Airport (BIA) (Box 13)
      - Bradley International Airport Commission (Box 13)
      - Bradley International Airport Business Express (Box 13)
      - Bradley International Fire Department's / EMNT's (Box 13)
      - Bradley International Master Ground (Box 13)
      - Groton/New London Airport (Box 13)
      - Sikorsky Airport - Bridgeport (Box 13)
      - Brainard Field - Hartford (Box 13)
      - Westchester County Airport (Box 13)
      - KLM Royal Dutch Airlines (Box 13)
      - USA - BIAS (Box 13)
      - Amtrak (Box 13)
      - Conrail - Consolidated Rail Corporation (Box 13)
      - Danbury Branch (Box 13)